Guide to the Stanford University, Department of East Asian Languages and Cultures, Honors Theses SC4-3651 SC4-3651
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of East Asian Languages and Cultures, honors theses
1992-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of East Asian Languages and Cultures
SC4-3651
1.25 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Dept. of East Asian Languages and Cultures.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of East Asian Languages and Cultures.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Acquisition Information
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Student papers.; East Asia -- Study and teaching.; Stanford University. Department of East Asian Languages and Cultures
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Hart, William T., Epiphany at Lushan: Zhou Enlai's shift for survival., 2007 (Box 1)
  - Heldt, Gustav Christopher, Lust for enlightenment: the body and Buddhist praxis in the Noh play Sotoba Komachi., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Kushida, Kenji, The Japanese wireless telecommunications industry: innovation, organizational structures, and government policy., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Leventhal, Eric M., In the name of equity: Japanese secondary students in crisis and the necessity for reconsideration of the current reform model., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Lopez, Sarah, The psychology of the single mother in the fiction of Tsushima Yûko., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Tan, Tie Wee, Consolidating separation: the policies of Lee Teng-hui and Chen Shui-bian towards the political status of Taiwan., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Tollerud, Suzanne, Beyond Beijing: American media coverage of China's 1989 demonstrations in the provinces., 2007 (Box 1)
  - Tsai, Robin, A view from the "other" side: majority/minority identity formation in southwest China., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Root, Megan, Corporate responsibility in Chinese companies: the legacy of socialism., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Harding, Sarah C., Cartwheels for China: a contemporary anthropological study set in Beijing, China, comparing the lifestyles of female gymnasts to those of non-athlete students., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Benson, Carey E., Gairaigo: Japanese and foreign, tradition and modernity in Japanese popular culture., 1998 (Box 2)
  - Lasker, Johanna, The transexuality of teaching: how to Japanese female teachers coordinate "female" language and authority?., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Fraleigh, Matthew, Confessions of the flesh: corporality in the literature of Mishima Yukio., 1994 (Box 2)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2015-039
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2018-060
  - Tsai, Sophia, "Changing societal dynamics in Japan: the rise of alternative general roles in Dramas", 2011 Jun 1 (Box 1)